INFORMATION

- gabrielmsantos.com.br
- (61) 99367-2608
- gabrielmarinhodossantoscd@gmail.com
- in /gabriel-marinho-bsb
- (gabrielMarinhocd/
- 🔘 Brasília DF Brazil

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- Nodejs
- React
- Angular
- Kotlin
- Java. JSP. Servlets
- SQLServer
- Scrum
- Docker
- Photoshop
- · Git, Github, Gitlab
- Wordpress, Elementor
- · Loja Integrada
- Tray

LANGUAGE

• English - Intermediary

EXTRAS

- Scrum Foundation Certificate
 (SFC) Certiprof
- Full Stacks Javascript
 Developer IGTI (MAI/20 a
 JUL/20)

PROFESSIONAL RESUME

I have a degree in systems analysis and development and I am studying an MBA in Mobile Developer. I have experience with Angular, React, Java, Kotlin, Wordpress, Photoshop and SQL. Currently I work as a Systems Analyst at SPA - Tecnologia e Inovação.

EXPERIENCES

SPA Tecnologia e Inovação - JR Systems Analyst MAR 2022 - NOW

• I work in the investigation, maintenance and correction of bugs in the school system using the languages and technologies: Java, Springboot, Angular and SQLServer, MVC, Scrum, Jekins.

Teige Brasil - Web Developer

FEV 2021 - JAN 2022

• I worked in the development of web pages HTML, CSS, Wordpress - Elementor, management of the hosting server, google services, domain registration and creation of virtual cards.

Project Ewines Brasil - Freelance Web Developer JUN 2021 - NOV 2021

 I worked on the development of a Tray ecommerce platform for a wine store, where products, customers and orders were migrated from the integrated store to Tray. The biggest challenge was using the integration with Mercado Livre, as the products had different names.

Project AWP Brasil - Full Stack Java Developer Freelancer JAN 2020 - ABR 2020

 I worked on the development of a technical assistance management system for UPS, using HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap, Mysql, Java jsp servlet. Documented the system providing UML, Use Cases, Logical Model, Sequence Diagram and Development Plan.

TRAINING

MBA - Mobile Developer - ICTI (Kotlin) JAN 2022 - AGO 2022

Systems Analysis and Development - UNIP FEV 2020 - DEC 2021

Computer Technician 1768 hours - ETB

FEV 2018 - DEC 2019